

duongvankhai2022001@gmail.com



Phương Cách, Quốc Oai, Hà Nôi



SKILLS

HTML & CSS

JAVASCRIPT

PHP

Laravel

MySQL

GitHub, Linux, Docker

EDUCATION

Major: Information and Technology TRANSPORTATION AND TECHNOLOGY UNIVERSITY GPA: 3.3/4.0 07/2019 - 06/2023

INDIVIDUAL PROJECTS

Soccer Store

10/2023 - 12/2023

Description: E-commerce website for a soccer store selling shoes

Link github:

- VueJS: https://github.com/imyourb ug/fe_aodabong
- Laravel: https://github.com/imyourbug/be_ aodabong

Technique: HTML/ CSS/JS, Laravel, VueJS, MySQL.

Detail:

- Designing and deciding on the visual layout of a website.
- Apply webservice architecture with FE is using VueJS and BE is Laravel.
- Using invoker controller pattern in Laravel to seperate each of action.
- Using third-party services such as: Facebook, Google to login, Paypal, VnPay to checkout,...
- Using VPS to publish the website, automatic deployment with FTP deploy,...

ABOUT ME

A junior developer with over 1.5 years of experience, and who would like to join a team of like-minded developers. Looking for a suitable position with a company where I can dedicate all of myself and learn more and more knowledge both of technology and life.

WORK EXPERIENCES

EXTREME VIÊT NAM - Fullstack Developer

AWS COST

01/2024 - present

(Build a website to display the cost of AWS Service)

- Get cost data from AWS by AWS Billing & Cost monitoring.
- Convert data to the specific format then display them on the website.
- Create the views to display the formatted data by the charts using the ChartJS library.
- Update code following the requests from customers.
- Write instructions for website operations.

#jquery #chartjs #aws

EXTREME VIÊT NAM - Backend Developer

PDL WEBVIEW

10/2013 - 01/2024

(Build APIs for PDL - an e-commerce application)

- Build the new APIs following the RestfulAPI.
- Create templates and export PDFs for the orders.
- Using docker to build an environment for coding.
- Deploy code to server weekly.
- Read and know the specs to code.
- Clear the problems in the specs by Q&A with the customer.
- Provide the solutions for the issues that happened in the coding process.
- Support tester to set up the environment, or prepare data for testing,...

#laravel #docker #mysql

EXTREME VIÊT NAM - Backend Developer

MAJICA APP

08/2022 - 10/2023

(Build and migrate APIs for Majica - an e-commerce application)

- Build the new APIs following the RestfulAPI and migrate the old APIs from the Zen framework.
- Using docker to build an environment for coding.
- Read and know the specs to code.
- Clear the problems in the specs by Q&A with the customer.

#laravel #docker #mysql

CERTIFICATES

TOEIC - 700 07/2023

INTERESTS

Play some kinds of sport such as: football, badminton, swimming,... or video games like PES,...